<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Curriculum Vitae</string>

    <string name="home_content">
        \n Android software development is the process by which new applications are created for devices running the Android operating system. Officially, apps can be written using Java, C++ or Kotlin using the Android software development kit. \n\n
        To build applications for the most popular operating system in the world and to grab the opportunity to put my apps on over 1 billion devices, I have chosen to become an Android Developer. My goal is to proceed with a career as an Android Developer. \n\n
         I am a creative Android developer with 4years of hands-on experience as an Android developer specializing in Java and web
programming. Adept at identifying the optimal technologies and solutions to achieve client goals, with a focus on automation
and new feature development. Skilled at handling requirements gathering, analysis, application design, programming,
testing, and implementation. Strong team collaborator working with cross-functional personnel on milestones. \n\n

         In the past I’ve been an invaluable contributor to the success of a wide range of software development projects,
particularly in mobile and web development. My involvement has been pivotal to the success of the software development
lifecycle, meeting and exceeding client requirements at each stage. \n\n

    </string>

    <string name="about_me"> \n
      I am a creative Android developer with 4years of hands-on experience as an Android developer specializing in Java and web
programming. Adept at identifying the optimal technologies and solutions to achieve client goals, with a focus on automation
and new feature development. Skilled at handling requirements gathering, analysis, application design, programming,
testing, and implementation. Strong team collaborator working with cross-functional personnel on milestones. \n\n

                <b>My skills include:</b>\n\n
 Developing Java and Android web and mobile applications. \n
 Evaluating and defining requirements. \n
 Identifying necessary application features. \n
 Programming core modules and functionality. \n
 Testing and troubleshooting applications. \n
 Creating templates to improve application development.


    </string>

    <string name = "experience">
        \n In the past I’ve been an invaluable contributor to the success of a wide range of software development projects,
particularly in mobile and web development. My involvement has been pivotal to the success of the software development
lifecycle, meeting and exceeding client requirements at each stage. \n\n

         <b>PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE</b> \n\n

        <b>CAREER NOTE:</b> \n Completed on-campus studies and currently taking distance education courses to complete a Master\'s
Degree in Computer Science (Available for full-time, W-2 employment). \n\n
<b>TECHNEPA PRIVATE LIMITED, Kathmandu, Bagmati, Nepal  2014-2018 </b> \n
Nepali IT company focused on web and mobile application development, SMS marketing, and FB advertising. \n\n
        <b>Java Developer</b> \n
Programmed a wide range of web applications using leading-edge technologies and tools.
Tasks: \n\n
 Handled full-lifecycle development of an Android game using AndEngine. \n
 Evaluated requirements to determine features. \n
 Coordinated web application programming and development. \n\n
<b>Achievement:</b> \n
 Defined template designs to streamline the development process. \n\n

<b>Technologies:</b> \n Java, HTML, CSS, JavaScript, JSP, Servlet, MS SQL, MySQL Server, Eclipse, IntelliJ, Android Studio,
Sublime Text, UML, XAMPP, Windows.

    </string>

    <string name = "contact">\n <b>Email:</b> \n niweshchandrarai@gmail.com \n
        ncrai@mum.edu \n\n
        <b>Mail Room No: </b> \n 121 \n\n
        <b>Mobile Number:</b> \n +17063060770 \n\n
        <b>Address:</b> \n 1000N 4th Street \n Fairfield, Iowa, USA \n\n</string>

    <string name="titleViewName">\n<b> Niwesh Chandra Rai</b> \n
        <b>Age: </b>24 \n
        <b>Worked At: </b> Technepa Pvt. Ltd.(2014-2018) \n
        <b>Fairfield, Iowa</b> \n\n
        <b>Short bio</b> \n\n

        Young and skilled Android Developer. \n
        4years of hands on experience(Java/Android).
    </string>

</resources>
